Guide to the Mandy Carter Papers, 1970-2013 RL.00195
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Gigs and Events Series, 1979-2013, 108 boxes
  - Call List, 2002 Jan. 26 (Box 168)
  - Meeting Masters, 2002 Jan. 26 (Box 168)
  - January 26th Meeting (People of Color: Freedom to Marry Organizing in Massachusetts), Roxbury, Mass., 2002 Jan. 26, 4 folders (Box 168)
  - Meeting with Robert Ochua-Schutz, Debrief Call with Evan, 2002 Jan. 28 (Box 168)
  - Dinner with Jackie, 2002 Jan. 29 (Box 168)
  - Speaking Gig, University of Connecticut, Storrs, Conn., 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 168)
  - Drive Home to Durham, 2002 Jan. 30 (Box 168)
  - Miscellaneous Emails, 2002 Jan. 31 (Box 168)
  - Last Day in Office, Packing Day, Boston, Mass., 2002 Feb. 1 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 3 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 4 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 5 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes/miscellaneous email exchanges, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 6 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 7 (Box 168)
  - Volvo Into Ingold, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 8 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 9 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 10 (Box 168)
  - Volvo In Shop, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 13 (Box 168)
  - Deye Appointment, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 14 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 15 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 18 (Box 168)
  - Daily Notes/miscellaneous email exchanges, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 20 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 21 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 22 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 25 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 26 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 27 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, Durham, N.C., 2002 Feb. 28 (Box 169)
  - Daily Notes, 2002 Mar. 1 (Box 169)
  - ACC Women's Tournament, Greensboro, N.C., 2002 Mar. 1-4 (Box 169)
  - UNC Vision Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 Mar. 5 (Box 169)
  - NCCR Board Retreat, San Francisco, Calif., 2002 Mar. 15-16 (Box 169)
  - NSD Reception, Washington, D.C., 2002 Mar. 20 (Box 169)
  - Patricia Warren of TBPG Meeting, Greensboro, N.C., 2002 Mar. 21 (Box 169)
  - Sharon Thompson Kick-off Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 Mar. 26, 2 folders (Box 169)
  - GSK First Friday Lunch, RTP, N.C., 2002 Apr. 5 (Box 169)
  - A3 Conference at Johnson C. Smith University, Charlotte, N.C., 2002 Apr. 6 (Box 169)
  - Elaine Marsham Fundraiser, Washington, D.C., 2002 Apr. 10 (Box 169)
  - Speaker at Triad Business and Professional Guild Meeting, Greensboro, N.C., 2002 Apr. 18 (Box 169)
  - Bob's Birthday Week, Schnectady, N.Y., 2002 Apr. 26-30 (Box 169)
  - NGLTF Creating Change 2002 Consulting Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2002 May 1 (Box 170)
  - Meeting with Jonathan at JCSU, Charlotte, N.C., 2002 May 15 (Box 170)
  - SC Pride 2002, Columbia, S.C., 2002 May 17-19 (Box 170)
  - Phone Interview with Heather Hiles re: same-sex marriage with POC view, 2002 May 31 (Box 170)
  - Cleveland Heights, Ohio Gig, Cleveland Heights, Oh., 2002 May or June (Box 170)
  - DC Pride Parade/Festival, Washington, D.C., 2002 June 8-9 (Box 170)
  - Traci West Interview, Durham-Raleigh, N.C., 2002 June 11, 2 folders (Box 170)
  - Tim from Save Dade in Durham, Durham, N.C., 2002 July 13 (Box 170)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 July 17 (Box 170)
  - B-Me Videotaping, Fayetteville, N.C., 2002 July 19 (Box 170)
  - Visit Germaine and Bob, Schnectady, N.Y., 2002 July 22-24 (Box 170)
  - 2nd Asot Mishpat Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2002 July 25-28 (Box 170)
  - Creating Connections Summer Program, 2002 July 30 (Box 170)
  - NABWMT Convention 2002, Miami Beach, Fla., 2002 Aug. 8-10 (Box 170)
  - Housesitting for Edie & Jackie, Gulfport, Fla., 2002 Aug-Oct (Box 170)
  - Save Dade Election, Miami, Fla., 2002 Sept. 10 (Box 170)
  - 2002 Out & Equal Workplace Summit, Orlando, Fla., 2002 Sept. 13-15 (Box 170)
  - Jennie Baughman Died, Downey, Calif., 2002 Oct. 1 (Box 170)
  - Domestic Violence Forum at NCCU, Durham, N.C., 2002 Oct. 17 (Box 170)
  - Newspaper Questions, 2002 Oct. 18 (Box 170)
  - SONG Research Project Conference Call, 2002 Oct. 21 (Box 170)
  - "Breaking the Queer Boundaries" at Duke University, Durham, N.C., 2002 Oct. 22 (Box 170)
  - Holly/Cris Concert, Durham, N.C., 2002 Oct. 26 (Box 170)
  - SONG Resume Submitted, Durham, N.C., 2002 Oct. 28 (Box 170)
  - Morehouse College Info, 2002 Nov. (Box 171)
  - NCOSH Yard Sale, Durham, N.C., 2002 Nov. 2 (Box 171)
  - Virtual Roundtable Piece (Box 171)
  - Creating Change 2002, Portland, Or., 2002 Nov. 5-10, 9 folders (Box 171)
  - Second NC Black Pride Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 Nov. 13 (Box 171)
  - SONG Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 Nov. 22-24 (Box 171)
  - GMAD Awards, New York, N.Y., 2002 Dec. 4 (Box 171)
  - SONG Job Interview, Durham, N.C., 2002 Dec. 11 (Box 171)
  - Statewide Anti-War Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 Dec. 14 (Box 171)
  - First HRC of POC Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2002 Dec. 28 (Box 171)
  - GLSEN Day of Silence, 2003 (Box 171)
  - Durham Bus to National Anti-War Rally, 2003 Jan. 18 (Box 171)
  - Durham's Work for Peace, Durham, N.C., 2003 Feb. 3 (Box 171)
  - SONG 10th Anniversary Celebration, Atlanta, Ga., 2003 Feb. 7 (Box 171)
  - NC Rally for Race & Justice, Raleigh, N.C., 2003 Feb. 15 (Box 171)
  - NCPJ Statewide Meeting, Charlotte, N.C., 2003 Mar. 29 (Box 172)
  - SC Pride 2003, Columbia, S.C., 2003 May 16-19 (Box 172)
  - Capital Pride Town Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2003 June 2 (Box 172)
  - NOA Meeting, 2003 June 4 (Box 172)
  - First Planning Meeting for 40th Anniversary of 1963 March on Washington, Durham, N.C., 2003 June 23 (Box 172)
  - Meeting with B-ME for Aug. 2nd Picnic, 2003 June 27 (Box 172)
  - 1st IWFR Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 July 7 (Box 172)
  - Black Workers for Justice Political Education Study, Raleigh, N.C., 2003 July 9 (Box 172)
  - DC Planning Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2003 July 11 (Box 172)
  - NOW National Conference, Arlington, Va., 2003 July 12 (Box 172)
  - WRL National Conference 80th Anniversary, Colorado Spring, Colo., 2003 July 17-20 (Box 172)
  - LGBT Community Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 July 23 (Box 172)
  - March on Washington Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2003 July 24 (Box 172)
  - Second IWFR Durham Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 July 29 (Box 172)
  - GSK "Brother Outsider", RTP, N.C., 2003 Aug. 1, 2 folders (Box 172)
  - Proud to Be Me Picnic Celebration, Fayetteville, N.C., 2003 Aug. 2 (Box 172)
  - 2nd MOW Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 Aug. 4 (Box 172)
  - SFC FSC Gathering, Atlanta, Ga., 2003 Aug. 13-15 (Box 173)
  - Fund for Southern Community Annual Meeting, Decatur, Ga., 2003 Aug. 15 (Box 173)
  - Community Forum, Washington, D.C., 2003 Aug. 21 (Box 173)
  - 40th Anniversary March on Washington, Washington, D.C., 2003 Aug. 21-23 (Box 173)
  - Rustin Film, Washington, D.C., 2003 Aug. 22 (Box 173)
  - Bayard Rustin Rally at 40th Anniversary March on Washington, Washington, D.C., 2003 Aug. 23, 2 folders (Box 173)
  - 6th Annual Civil Rights Conference at Kenda's, Washington, D.C., 2003 Aug. 24 (Box 173)
  - Dialog/Facilitation UNC-CH, Durham, N.C., 2003 Aug. 30 (Box 173)
  - IWFR Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 4 (Box 173)
  - Democracy Project, 2003 Sept. 5 (Box 173)
  - IWFR Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 10 (Box 173)
  - IWFR Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 16 (Box 173)
  - Pride At Work Convention, Tyson's Corner, Va., 2003 Sept. 18-20 (Box 173)
  - NC NOW State Conference, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 173)
  - WHAT Radio Interview with Rita Adessa, Philadelphia, Pa., 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 173)
  - NC Pride Fest 2003, Duke East Campus, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 174)
  - Durham Peace Committee, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 22 (Box 174)
  - IWFR Press Conference/IWFR Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 23 (Box 174)
  - IWFR Meeting/Press Work, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 29 (Box 174)
  - IWFR, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept. 30 (Box 174)
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, Durham, N.C., 2003 Sept./Oct. (Box 174)
  - October 2003 (Box 174)
  - "Power of the Vote" Night at Spektrum, Fayetteville, N.C., 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 174)
  - South Carolina ProNet Conference, Beaufort, S.C., 2003 Oct. 4-5 (Box 174)
  - SONG Women's Retreat, Highlander Center, New Market, Tenn., 2003 Oct. 10-12, 3 folders (Box 174)
  - SONG Board Meeting, Highlander Center, New Market, Tenn., 2003 Oct. 12 (Box 174)
  - National Conference, NCADP, Nashville, Tenn., 2003. Oct. 17-19 (Box 174)
  - Brown Bag Lunch with Nick Wood of FLOC, Durham, N.C., 2003 Oct. 21 (Box 175)
  - Elon College, Elon, N.C., 2003 Oct. 21 (Box 175)
  - Alliance for Justice Training, Durham, N.C., 2003 Oct. 22 (Box 175)
  - UC-Davis Pride Week, Davis, Calif., 2003 Oct. 22-24 (Box 175)
  - Mobilization Against War, Washington, D.C., 2003 Oct. 25 (Box 175)
  - SONG Volunteer Day, Durham, N.C., 2003 Oct. 26 (Box 175)
  - Albany Awards Dinner, Albany, N.Y., 2003 Oct. 28-30 (Box 175)
  - Mandy's Birthday/SONG Event, Gulfport, Fla., 2003 Nov. 2 (Box 175)
  - NGLTF Creating Change, Miami Beach, Fla., 2003 Nov. 5-9, 2 folders (Box 175)
  - Anti-NAFTA Rally, Greensboro, N.C., 2004 Jan. 10 (Box 176)
  - Cary DP Meeting, Cary, N.C., 2004 Jan. 14 (Box 176)
  - Bayard Rustin/Pat Parker Leadership Reception, Atlanta, Ga., 2004 Jan. 16 (Box 176)
  - GLSEN SOCO Conference, Durham, N.C., 2004 Jan. 16-18 (Box 176)
  - ITLA MLK Weekend, Atlanta, Ga., 2004 Jan. 16-18 (Box 176)
  - "Beat Bush" Meeting, Knightsdale, N.C., 2004 Jan. 18 (Box 176)
  - Durham MLK March SONG BRCA Contingent, Durham, N.C., 2004 Jan. 19 (Box 176)
  - March for Women's Lives "Meet up" for April 25, 2004, Raleigh, N.C., 2004 Jan. 20 (Box 176)
  - Astro Data Services May, Durham, N.C., 2004 Jan. 22 (Box 176)
  - Lambda Legal, 2004 Jan. 23 (Box 176)
  - Peace Meeting, Greensboro, N.C., 2004 Jan. 24 (Box 176)
  - 2nd Meeting with Roselle Eaton re: SONG Website, 2004 Jan. 25 (Box 176)
  - Cal State, San Bernardino, Calif., 2004 Jan. 31 (Box 176)
  - Triangle Freedom to Marry Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 3 (Box 176)
  - Amin Interview on 4 March on Washingtons, Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 6 (Box 176)
  - SURGE Conference, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2004 Feb. 6-8 (Box 176)
  - Southwest Texas State University--San Marcos, Austin, Tex., 2004 Feb. 11 (Box 176)
  - Leadership Durham, Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 13 (Box 176)
  - "A Conversation on Race," Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 14, 2 folders (Box 176)
  - NC Progressive Dems Meeting, Pittsboro, N.C., 2004 Feb. 14 (Box 177)
  - Immigrant Rights Rally, Goldsboro, N.C., 2004 Feb. 21 (Box 177)
  - UU Church Greensboro, Greensboro, N.C., 2004 Feb. 22 (Box 177)
  - POC NV Network Call, 2004 Feb. 23 (Box 177)
  - Federal Marriage Amendment Civil Disobedience Call, 2004 Feb. 23 (Box 177)
  - St. Cloud Gig, St. Cloud, Minn., 2004 Feb. 23-27 (Box 177)
  - Triangle FTM Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 24 (Box 177)
  - Anti-Discrimination State Law Forum, NCCU, Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 25 (Box 177)
  - Hispanic Democrats of NC, Durham, N.C., 2004 Feb. 28 (Box 177)
  - UNC-G Pride Brown Bag Lunch, Greensboro, N.C., 2004 Mar. 3 (Box 177)
  - Freedom to Marry Civil Disobedience Call, 2004 Mar. 8 (Box 177)
  - AFFA Dinner, Charleston, S.C., 2004 Mar. 9 (Box 177)
  - Lunch Meeting with NC Community Shares, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 10 (Box 177)
  - 2nd NGLTF POCOI Retreat, Oakland, Calif., 2004 Mar. 12-14 (Box 177)
  - Curve Magazine Article, San Francisco, Calif., 2004 Mar. 15 (Box 177)
  - United For Peace, 2004 Mar. 20 (Box 177)
  - "World Still Says No To War," Fayetteville, N.C., 2004 Mar. 20 (Box 177)
  - B-Me-SONG Meeting, Fayetteville, N.C., 2004 Mar. 22 (Box 177)
  - NC Equality/HRC Marriage Town Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2004 Mar. 24 (Box 177)
  - NGLTF NPRT, Washington, D.C., 2004 Mar. 25 (Box 177)
  - November Pledge Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 25 (Box 177)
  - NC Public Allies Training, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 26 (Box 178)
  - Unity 2004 Conference, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2004 Mar. 26-28 (Box 178)
  - MFWL Night of Entertainment for April 25, 2004, Greensboro, N.C., 2004 Mar. 27 (Box 178)
  - GLSEN-SONG POC LGBT Media Day, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 28 (Box 178)
  - SONG-GLAAD Marriage Equality Media Training, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 28 (Box 178)
  - TFTM/SONG Media Day, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 29 (Box 178)
  - Lunch Meeting with Cheryl NC Community Shares, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 30 (Box 178)
  - NC March Against Madness Tour, Durham, N.C., 2004 Mar. 31 (Box 178)
  - GLSEN Conference, Boston, Mass., 2004 Apr. 3, 2 folders (Box 178)
  - Northeast NOW Regional Conference, Providence, R.I., 2004 Apr. 4 (Box 178)
  - Pilgramage for Peace Justice, Morgantown/Raleigh, N.C., 2004 Apr. 4-9 (Box 178)
  - Voices for Working Families, 2004 Apr. 7 (Box 178)
  - NC Marriage Summit Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Apr. 9 (Box 178)
  - Marriage Equality Panel, Guilford College, Greensboro, N.C., 2004 Apr. 14 (Box 178)
  - 15th Anniversary ED Retreat, Laguna Beach, Calif., 2004 Apr. 15-18 (Box 179)
  - National March for Women's Lives, Washington, D.C., 2004 Apr. 25, 9 folders (Box 179)
  - Southern Funding Collaborative Site Visit, Durham, N.C., 2004 Apr. 28 (Box 179)
  - Incite Women of Color Conference, Santa Barbara, Calif., 2004 Apr. 30-May 1 (Box 179)
  - TSU GSA Weekend/Highlander, 2004 May 1-2 (Box 179)
  - TFTM Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 May 6 (Box 179)
  - Democracy Project Training, Durham, N.C., 2004 May 7 (Box 179)
  - Democracy Project SONG-LGCCP, Charlotte, N.C., 2004 May 8 (Box 179)
  - AVS Vigil-Rally, Charleston, S.C., 2004 May 9 (Box 179)
  - Queer Space Summer Group Program, Richmond, Va., 2004 May 12 (Box 180)
  - Senate Democrats Meeting 2004 Elections, Washington, D.C., 2004 May 13 (Box 180)
  - NCBI LGBT Leadership Training, San Marcos, Tex., 2004 May 13-16 (Box 180)
  - 2nd National Strategy Meeting of LGBTST Organizations Against the War or Terrorism, Philadelphia, Pa., 2004 May 14-16 (Box 180)
  - SC Pride 2004, Columbia, S.C., 2004 May 14-15 (Box 180)
  - "Don't Amend Rally," Washington, D.C., 2004 May 17 (Box 180)
  - Gill Meetings, Denver, Colo., 2004 May 18-19 (Box 180)
  - NC Drivers License and Immigrants, Durham, N.C., 2004 May 20 (Box 180)
  - Together in Faith Conference, Ypsilanti, Mich., 2004 May 21-22 (Box 180)
  - Post April 25th Town Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 May 24 (Box 180)
  - NOA East Refund Meeting, Black Mountain, N.C., 2004 May 27-30 (Box 180)
  - NBJC Board Meeting (in person), Washington, D.C., 2004 May 28 (Box 180)
  - EPF Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2004 May 28 (Box 180)
  - Public Allies Interviews, Durham, N.C., 2004 June 16 (Box 181)
  - November Pledge Kick-off, 2004 June 17 (Box 181)
  - ACLU Meeting and NBJC, New York, N.Y., 2004 June 18 (Box 181)
  - SAGE National Conference, New York, N.Y., 2004 June 18-20, 2 folders (Box 181)
  - Pullen Baptist Churches Marriage Panel, Raleigh, N.C., 2004 June 20 (Box 181)
  - Atlanta Pride 2004, Atlanta, Ga., 2004 June 25-27 (Box 181)
  - California FTM Retreat, Berkeley, Calif., 2004 June 28 (Box 181)
  - Richmond HB 751 Rally, Richmond, Va., 2004 June 30 (Box 181)
  - 2004 ACLU Membership Conference, San Francisco, Calif., 2004 July 6-8, 2 folders (Box 181)
  - SONG 14-person July Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 July 9-11, 2 folders (Box 181)
  - 95th NAACP Convention, Philadelphia, Pa., 2004 July 10-15, 3 folders (Box 182)
  - Fayetteville Marriage Equality, Fayetteville, N.C., 2004 July 17 (Box 182)
  - 24th NABWMT Convention, Atlanta, Ga., 2004 July 17-24 (Box 182)
  - San Diego Pride, San Diego, Calif., 2004 July 30-31 (Box 182)
  - Little Rock Meeting, Little Rock, Ark., 2004 July 31 (Box 182)
  - PAC Fundraising Training, Durham, N.C., 2004 Aug. 3 (Box 182)
  - SONG Women's Retreat, Prospect, Ky., 2004 Aug. 6-8 (Box 182)
  - Tara Purohit Meetingm, NC Vote, Durham, N.C., 2004 Aug. 11 (Box 182)
  - Gill Interview with Linda Bush, Durham, N.C., 2004 Aug. 11 (Box 182)
  - NC Progressive Vote Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Aug. 12 (Box 182)
  - 9th NC Gay Lesbian Film Festival, Durham, N.C., 2004 Aug. 12-15 (Box 182)
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Planning Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Aug. 13 (Box 182)
  - Kopkind Weekend, Guilford, Vt., 2004 Aug. 20-22 (Box 182)
  - Winston-Salem FTM Panel, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2004 Aug. 23 (Box 182)
  - NC Women United, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2004 Aug. 23 (Box 182)
  - UUW's Marriage Panel, Winston-Salem, N.C., 2004 Aug. 23 (Box 182)
  - HRC Gospel and Soul, Detroit, Mich., 2004 Aug. 28 (Box 183)
  - IFBP South Regional Meeting, Atlanta, Ga., 2004 Sept. 4 (Box 183)
  - Davina/Charlotte/FTM Panel, Charlotte, N.C., 2004 Sept. 7 (Box 183)
  - Freedom to Marry Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2004 Sept. 10-11 (Box 183)
  - Marriage Equality Conference, Fayetteville, Ark., 2004 Sept. 26 (Box 183)
  - NC Pride 2004, Durham, N.C., 2004 Oct. 2 (Box 183)
  - 10th Anniversary HRC Gala, Durham, N.C., 2004 Oct. 2 (Box 183)
  - SONG 10th Anniversary Gathering, St. Helena Island, S.C., 2004 Oct. 8-11 (Box 183)
  - National Rally for Marriage Equality, Washington, D.C., 2004 Oct. 11 (Box 183)
  - Peace and Justice Studies Association (PJSA) 2004, San Francisco, Calif., 2004 Oct. 13-17, 2 folders (Box 183)
  - NCDAAP Workshop, Washington, D.C., 2004 Oct. 15 (Box 183)
  - Lake Michigan College Gig, Benton Harbor, Mich., 2004 Oct. 20-21 (Box 183)
  - 2nd Annual B-ME/SONG Picnic, Fayetteville, N.C., 2004 Oct. 23 (Box 183)
  - Alliance for Justice/NC Democracy Project, 2004 Oct. 23 (Box 183)
  - NYU Gig, New York, N.Y., 2004 Oct. 25-26 (Box 184)
  - Southern Funding Collaborative, Knoxville, Tenn., 2004 Nov. 7-9 (Box 184)
  - Creating Change 2004, St. Louis, Mo., 2004 Nov. 9-14, 4 folders (Box 184)
  - ME Forum, Lake Michigan College, Benton Harbor, Mich., 2004 Nov. 14 (Box 184)
  - Winning the Freedom to Marry, [2004 Nov.?] (Box 184)
  - New Women's Movement Meeting, Chicago, Ill., 2004 Nov. 17-20, 3 folders (Box 184)
  - November 20th Planning Mtg for March 19, 2005 Action, Fayetteville, N.C., 2004 Nov. 20 (Box 185)
  - Charlotte Black Pride Meet & Greet, Charlotte, N.C., 2004 Dec. 1 (Box 185)
  - Fourth World War Screening, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2004 Dec. 2 (Box 185)
  - Durham County Women's Agenda Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2004 Dec. 3 (Box 185)
  - Progressive Dialogue III, Washington, D.C., 2004 Dec. 4-5 (Box 185)
  - Richard Nathan Trust Closing, New York, N.Y., 2004 Dec. 6-7, 2 folders (Box 185)
  - 1st Durham Meeting for Fayetteville Action, Durham, N.C., 2004 Dec. 8 (Box 185)
  - Speaker International Human Rights Day, Raleigh, N.C., 2004 Dec. 10 (Box 185)
  - SONG/Ladyslipper Holiday Sale, Durham, N.C., 2004 Dec. 10-11 (Box 185)
  - Meeting with Kara at SONG, Durham, N.C., 2004 Dec. 14 (Box 185)
  - Palmetto Umoja Meeting, Columbia, S.C., 2004 Dec. 18 (Box 185)
  - NCRC4ME Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2004 Dec. 21 (Box 185)
  - Southern Funding Collaborative Grantee Gathering, Tunica, Miss., 2005 Apr. 25-27 (Box 185)
  - New Women's Movement, Movement Building & Strategic Collaborations for the Future, Lake Bluff, Ill., 2005 May 9-11 (Box 185)
  - Movement Building and Marriage: A Dialogue About Collaboration, 2005 Aug. 5 (Box 185)
  - Exit Interview Mtg #1, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 6 (Box 186)
  - Final Fayetteville Bayard Rustin Meeting, Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Jan. 6 (Box 186)
  - 3rd Check-in Call NBJC Minister's Conference, 2006 Jan. 10 (Box 186)
  - Chuck Fager Reading: 1st Annual FBRCA, Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Jan. 12 (Box 186)
  - Fayetteville MLK Parade: Post Parade Chili & Program, Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Jan. 14 (Box 186)
  - Duke MLK Event, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 16 (Box 186)
  - UNC Women's Center MLK Event, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2006 Jan. 17 (Box 186)
  - NBJC Black Church Summit, Atlanta, Ga., 2006 Jan. 19-21, 2 folders (Box 186)
  - Workshop with Harry, 2006 Jan. 20 (Box 186)
  - Workshop with TIB, Tonyia, 2006 Jan. 21 (Box 186)
  - Durham AOCD Team Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 25 (Box 186)
  - Post-Fayetteville BRCA Meeting, Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Jan. 27 (Box 186)
  - SONG Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 27-29 (Box 186)
  - SONG Event for ME-New Beginnings, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 28 (Box 186)
  - Ladyslipper Board Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 31 (Box 186)
  - Precinct 8 State of Union Watch Party, Durham, N.C., 2006 Jan. 31 (Box 186)
  - 2nd Preceptors Lunch Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Feb. 1 (Box 186)
  - Basic Rights Oregon Trip, Portland, Or., 2006 Feb. 3-5 (Box 186)
  - 4th Kate Clinton Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Feb. 6 (Box 186)
  - ISC Conference Call, Durham, N.C., 2006 Feb. 7 (Box 186)
  - University of Arizona Awareness Week, Tucson, Ariz., 2006 Feb. 13-17 (Box 186)
  - Precinct 8 Annual Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Feb. 21 (Box 186)
  - Gill Foundation Conference Call, 2006 Feb. 24 (Box 186)
  - NCCU Vagina Monologues, Durham, N.C., 2006 Feb. 24 (Box 186)
  - Pacific School of Belgium Call, 2006 Feb. 28 (Box 186)
  - Emory University Keynote, Atlanta, Ga., 2006 Mar. 2 (Box 187)
  - RBJC Religious Outreach Call, 2006 Mar. 9 (Box 187)
  - Peggy Lynch Screens "Brother Outside," Detroit, Mich., 2006 Mar. 12 (Box 187)
  - Duke Student Oral History Project, Durham, N.C., 2006 Mar. 12 (Box 187)
  - 5th Kate Clinton Concert Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 Mar. 13 (Box 187)
  - US Senate LGBT Outreach, Washington, D.C., 2006 Mar. 16 (Box 187)
  - John D'Emilio for NC GALA, Durham, N.C., 2006 Mar. 17 (Box 187)
  - 3rd Annual "World Says no to War," Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Mar. 18 (Box 187)
  - Southern Organizers Conference, Fayetteville, N.C., 2006 Mar. 19 (Box 187)
  - Curve Magazine Interview, 2006 Mar. 21 (Box 187)
  - Astraea Foundation Orientation Call-US Funding Panel, 2006 Mar. 21 (Box 187)
  - 3nd New Women's Movement Retreat, Chicago, Ill., 2006 Mar. 22-24, 2 folders (Box 187)
  - NBJC Board Meeting, Washington, D.C., 2006 Mar. 24-26 (Box 187)
  - George Mason University Vision Awards, Fairfax, Va., 2006 Mar. 25 (Box 187)
  - Durham Response Network, 2006 Mar. 27 (Box 187)
  - "Toilet Training" Video/Discussion, Raleigh, N.C., 2006 Mar. 27 (Box 187)
  - University of Louisvile Diversity Panel, Louisville, Ky., 2006 Apr. 2-5 (Box 188)
  - Xavier University, Cincinnati, Oh., 2006 Apr. 4 (Box 188)
  - Transylvania University, Lexington, Ky., 2006 Apr. 5 (Box 188)
  - Leadership Durham 2006 Diveristy Panel, Durham, N.C., 2006 Apr. 6 (Box 188)
  - UNC LGBT Unity Conference 2006, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2006 Apr. 7-9 (Box 188)
  - Durham County Convention Pct 8, Durham, N.C., 2006 Apr. 8 (Box 188)
  - FTM Collaborative Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2006 Apr. 10 (Box 188)
  - Marcie's Class-Long Haul Organizing, Chapel Hill, N.C., 2006 Apr. 17 (Box 188)
  - AOCD Durham LBW Team Forum, Durham, N.C., 2006 Apr. 22 (Box 188)
  - SWOOP Emcee Walk Through Meeting, Durham, N.C., 2006 May 2 (Box 188)
  - Out and Equal Community Meeting, Raleigh, N.C., 2006 May 4 (Box 188)
  - Kate Clinton in Concert, Durham, N.C., 2006 May 7 (Box 188)
  - NGLTF "Moral Values" Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2006 May 10 (Box 188)
  - CampOut-Roan Mountain Park, Roan Mountain, Tenn., 2006 May 13-14 (Box 188)
  - POC Lobby Day Briefing, Durham, N.C., 2006 May 17 (Box 188)
  - 15th SC Pride, Columbia, S.C., 2006 May 19-21 (Box 189)
  - Meeting with Asha Leong, Columbia, S.C., 2006 May 22-23 (Box 189)
  - SCEC Message, 2006 (Box 189)
  - Spencer Hope David Podcast, Raleigh, N.C., 2006 May 25 (Box 189)
  - Knoxville Queer Film Festival, Knoxville, Tenn., 2006 June 2-4 (Box 189)
  - Astraea US Fund Panel Meeting, New York, N.Y., 2006 June 2-4, 8 folders (Box 189)
    Includes materials related to ALLGO, Appalachian Women's Alliance, Center for Artistic Revolution, Incite!, and OLOC.
  - 2nd Face to Face Asha Meeting, Columbia, S.C., 2006 June 5-6 (Box 189)
  - Roots and Wings Dialogue, Greensboro, N.C., 2006 June 11 (Box 189)